current: n.   电流, sculpture: n.   雕塑
Lesson 18. Electric currents in modern art. Modern sculpture rarely surprises us anymore.
第18课。现代艺术中的电流。现代雕塑很少会让我们感到惊讶。
mistaken: adj. 错误的
The idea that modern art can only be seen in museums is mistaken. Even people who take no interest
现代艺术只能在博物馆中看到的想法是错误的。甚至不感兴趣的人
sculpture: n.   雕塑
in art cannot have failed to notice examples of modern sculpture. On display in public places,
在艺术中​​，不可能没有注意到现代雕塑的例子。在公共场所展出，
strange forms stand in gardens. And outside buildings and shops. We have got quite used to them.
奇怪的形式站在花园中。以及外部建筑物和商店。我们已经习惯了他们。
Some so-called modern pieces have been on display for nearly 80 years.
一些所谓的现代作品已经展出了将近80年。
sculpture: n.   雕塑, exhibit: n.   展品，陈列品
In spite of this, some people, including myself, were surprised by a recent exhibition of modern sculpture.
尽管如此，包括我本人在内的某些人对最近的现代雕塑展览感到惊讶。
gallery: n.   美术馆
The first thing I saw when I entered the art gallery was a notice which said,
我进入美术馆时看到的第一件事是通知说：
exhibit: n.   展品，陈列品
do not touch the exhibits. Some of them are dangerous. The objects on display were pieces of moving
不要触摸展览。其中一些很危险。展示的对象是移动的一部分
sculpture: n.   雕塑
sculpture. Oddly shaped forms that are suspended form the ceiling and move in response to a gust of
雕塑。奇怪形状的形式，悬浮形式的天花板和响应的阵风移动
wind are. Quite familiar to everybody. These objects, however, were different, lined up against the
风是。每个人都很熟悉。但是，这些物体不同，与
attach: v.   连，系, sphere: n.   球体, magnetize: v.   使磁化
wall. There were long thin wires attached to metal spheres. The spheres had been magnetized and
墙。金属球上有很长的细线。球被磁化了，
repel: v.   排斥
attracted or repelled each other all the time. In the center of the hall, there were a number of
一直吸引或击退。在大厅的中心，有很多
flicker: v.   闪烁
tall structures which contained colored lights. These lights flickered continuously like traffic
高的结构，其中包含彩色灯光。这些灯像流量一样连续闪烁
emit: v.   放射, flash: v.   闪光
lights which have gone mad. Sparks were emitted from small black boxes and red lamps flashed on
生气的灯。火花是从小黑盒子和红色灯闪烁的
exhibit: n.   展品，陈列品, prehistoric: adj. 史前的，老掉牙的, electronic: adj. 电子的
and off angrily. It was rather like an exhibition of prehistoric electronic equipment. These
愤怒地。这就像史前电子设备的展览。这些
peculiar: adj. 奇异的, shock: v.   令人震惊，刺激人, emotionally: adv. 事情上
peculiar forms not only seemed designed to shock people emotionally, but to give them electric shocks as well.
奇特的形式不仅旨在使人们在情感上震惊，而且还给他们带来了电击。